question_data = [

         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
